valleyvet.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Statement - ValleyVet.com

Last Updated: August 16, 2018.

### Introduction

This privacy policy applies to all website and mobile applications linking to or posting this privacy policy that are operated by Valley Veterinary Clinic, Ltd., d/b/a Valley Vet Supply ("Valley Vet," "us," "we," or "our"), which are collectively referred to in this privacy policy as the Site.

In this privacy policy, we describe Valley Vet's practices for collecting, storing, using, and disclosing the personal and other information that we may obtain about you through the Site, or through your other communications with Valley Vet. Please note that by using or accessing the Site, or communicating with Valley Vet by telephone, mail, email, or otherwise, you consent to the collection, storage, use, and disclosure practices described in this privacy policy.

For ease of reference, you may click on any of the following links to jump to one of the topics addressed in this privacy policy: 

  * Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information We Collect
  * When Information We Collect May Be Disclosed to Third Parties
  * Security Measures for Information We Collect
  * How to Correct or Update Information We Have Collected About You
  * How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals
  * Transfer of Data from Outside the United States
  * Children
  * Privacy Policies of any Linked Website or Other Parties
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * Governing Law, Jurisdiction, and Dispute Resolution
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * Contact Us

### Information We Collect

  * Purchases and Other Financial Transactions. When you make a purchase or engage in any other financial transaction, you will be asked to provide information necessary to facilitate the transaction, such as your name, credit card or debit card number, associated security code, telephone number, billing address, email address, and shipping address.
  * Program Registration. In connection with your registration or other interaction online with one of our programs, you may be asked to provide certain personal information, such as your name, email address, mailing address, and date of birth or age-as well as information about your pet-and to create a user name and password.
  * Sign-Up for Emails, Newsletters, or Other Correspondence. If you sign up on the Site to receive email communications, newsletters, or other correspondence from us, you may be asked to provide us with your name, email address, and mailing address, along with other information related to your subscription or correspondence.
  * Contests, Sweepstakes, and Other Promotions. We may collect information about you when you participate in a promotion that we sponsor, such as a contest or sweepstakes (which we may sponsor alone, or co-sponsor with one or more third parties). To participate in one of our promotions, you may be asked to provide your name, email address, mailing address, and other contact information. For some promotions, we may request other information about you as well. Your participation will be subject to the official rules of the promotion, as well as this privacy policy, and the privacy policy of any co-sponsor.
  * Interactive Forums. You and other users may be allowed to post comments and other content on certain portions of the Site, such as on a discussion board, blog, or other interactive forum. We may collect any information that you or another user posts about you on the Site-including personal information about you-and it may be available to all users who have access to the Site. Please keep this in mind when considering what information to post to the Site.
  * Social Networking Activities. The Site may include the ability for you and other users to link to one or more social networking platforms (such as Facebook or Twitter). We may receive information about you when you choose to post or otherwise share information about us on any of these social networking platforms. Any information that you or others post to a social networking platform will be accessible by any users of the platform, subject to its terms of service and privacy policy.
  * Social Sign-In. The Site may incorporate functionality enabling you to sign-on using your login information from a social networking platform, in lieu of creating a new login account specifically for the Site. If we incorporate such functionality and you use it to sign into the Site, we may collect information about you from the social networking platform, such as your list of friends, "likes," and interests, as well as your contact information.
  * Usage Data. When you use or access the Site, we may collect certain usage data generated by your activities on the Site, including your purchasing history, credit card chargeback data, pages viewed, number of bytes transferred, hyperlinks clicked, and other actions you take on the Site. The Site may also track the URL that you visit before you come to the Site, the URL that you go to next, and your Internet Protocol (IP) address or mobile device identifier.
  * Location and Device Data. We collect information about your location, such as the approximate location of your computer, phone, or other device (geolocation)from which you access the Site, as well as your IP address, and related data. We may associate information we collect from your different devices, which helps us provide consistent services and experiences across your devices. Some examples of the device information we collect are attributes such as the operating system, hardware version, device settings, file and software names and types, battery and signal strength, and device identifiers; device locations, including geographic locations through GPS, Bluetooth, or WiFi signals; and connection information such as the name of your mobile operator or ISP, browser type, language and time zone, mobile phone number, and IP address.
  * Online Information-Gathering Tools. We use cookies, mobile advertising identifiers, web beacons, and other online information-gathering tools in connection with the Site-including Google advertising cookies and identifiers to enable the collection of Google Analytics data for web traffic on the Site. These tools are intended to make using the Site easier in various ways, such as saving your preferences for you. We may also use cookies to deliver content tailored to your interests. If your browser is set to reject cookies, or if your browser notifies you that you are about to receive a cookie and you reject it, then your use of the Site may not be as efficient as if the cookies were enabled. For example, if you have chosen to enable Google to associate your web and app browsing history with your Google account, and to use information from your Google account to personalize ads, Google will use data from you while signed-in to your Google account (personal information), together with Google Analytics advertising cookies and identifiers to tailor ads to your indicated preferences, across your devices. We do not share information that personally identifies you (information such as your name or email address that can by itself be used to contact or identify you) with advertising measurement or analytics partners unless you give us permission. We may provide these partners with information about the reach and effectiveness of their advertising without providing information that personally identifies you, or if we have aggregated the information so that it does not personally identify you. You may [opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) of Google Analytics by following Google's [opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) instructions.
  * Third-Party Integrated Services. We may incorporate third-party ads and other third-party content on the Site, and integrate other third-party offerings into the Site, enabling certain such third parties to collect information about you or your online activities across other websites and, over time, through your use of the Site. For example, Google uses cookies to serve the Google Reviews badge on the Site, and to serve ads based on your prior visits to the Site. You may opt-out of Google's use of cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to the Site by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). Except as otherwise described in this privacy policy, any information collected through such integrated technologies is collected directly by these third parties for use by such third parties and other authorized parties, subject to the privacy policies of those other parties.
  * Online Inquiries and Correspondence. When you submit an inquiry or otherwise correspond through the Site, you may be asked to provide your name, email address, and other personal information to us.

We may keep the information we collect about you indefinitely.

### How We Use Information We Collect

We may use information we collect about you for a variety of commercial purposes. For example, we may use such information to: 

  * process payment transactions and provide fraud detection, prevention, and scoring services;
  * administer and improve the Site and businesses;
  * promote our products and services to you, as well as the products and services of our affiliates;
  * promote, and enable the promotion of third-party products and services to you that we think you may find interesting and valuable;
  * deliver email communications, newsletters, and other correspondence to which you subscribe;
  * communicate with you about our contests, sweepstakes, and other promotions;
  * conduct other marketing activities;
  * communicate with you regarding your membership in one of our programs, and facilitate the functioning of our programs; and
  * respond to your inquiries and other correspondence, or request that you provide feedback to us.

### When Information We Collect May Be Disclosed to Third Parties

We disclose to third parties the personal or other information collected about you either (1) when we have otherwise secured your permission to do so, or (2) in any of the following situations, with your permission based on this disclosure: 

  * We may share your order information with select vendors and manufacturers to assist them in their sales and marketing efforts; to facilitate reporting and information sharing regarding adverse drug events and disease control; and to expedite rebate calculation and payment services. For example, we may share the quantities of products you purchase; your full name; your HIN (Health Industry Number); your bill-to and ship-to addresses; your zip code; the date of sale; the invoice number; and the unit quantity and sales price per product and per order.
  * We may share the information collected about you within the Valley Vet family of companies-which means we may disclose the information collected about you to our affiliates, subject to the terms of this privacy policy.
  * We may disclose the information collected about you to our third-party contractors and partners in connection with their performance of services or other activities in support of the Site and our businesses, or their completing or confirming on our behalf a transaction or series of transactions that you conduct with us. For example, your credit or debit card number and expiration date, name, address, transaction amount, chargeback data, browsing and transaction history, computer location, and IP address and related data may be collected and provided to our merchant payment processor and its vendors, agents, suppliers, and contractors for the purpose of processing payment transactions and providing fraud detection, prevention, and scoring services.
  * Information about you that is collected by third-party ads, content, or technologies integrated with the Site may be disclosed to such third parties.
  * We may disclose the results of aggregated data about you and other users of the Site without restriction. In these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you.
  * We may disclose to one or more third parties the information collected about you as part of a potential or complete merger, acquisition, or other sale or transfer of any of the assets or business of Valley Vet, or any of our affiliates. Please note that the entity receiving such information in connection with one of these transactions may not comply with all of the terms of this privacy policy.
  * We may disclose information about you to the government or to other third parties to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders, and subpoenas or other legal process, such as in connection with suspected illegal activity associated with the Site or our business. We reserve the right to release information collected through the Site to law enforcement or other government officials, as we determine to be necessary or appropriate.
  * We may also disclose information about you to third parties if needed to enforce any of the terms of use or other agreements for the Site, or any investigation of potential violations of those agreements; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; to protect against harm to the Site; or to protect our rights, property, or safety, or the rights, property, or safety of our users or others (for example, to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection).

### Security Measures for Information We Collect

To help protect the privacy of information we collect, we employ security measures that are intended to be consistent with industry best practices. In storing such information, we take commercially reasonable steps intended to protect such data against unauthorized access. But please be aware that the Site is operated on software, hardware, and networks, and any component may experience breaches of security or other problems beyond our control that may compromise the security of information collected about you.

Please also be aware that despite our best intentions and the guidelines outlined in this privacy policy, no data transmission over the Internet or via a Wi-Fi network, or any encryption method, can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Thus, it may be possible for third parties not under Valley Vet's control to intercept or access your personal information transmitted through the Site or via email. We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of all information you provide through the Site, but due to the inherent nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any such information will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others who do not have your authorization. Any such transmission of information about you to Valley Vet is at your own risk.

### How to Correct or Update Information We Have Collected About You

You may correct or update information we have collected about you by contacting us at the email or mailing address noted at the end of this privacy policy, or, if available on the Site, by editing your information and preferences on your Account Information page on the Site. You may also unsubscribe from any email subscriptions by following the applicable "unsubscribe" link. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to update our files to reflect your request as promptly as possible.

We may retain original and updated information for reasons such as technical constraints, dispute resolution, compliance with laws, fraud prevention, troubleshooting, and enforcement of our terms of use and other agreements. Also, please note that we cannot update any information about you collected through the Site that has already been disclosed (as permitted under this privacy policy) to a third party.

### How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals

The Site does not currently support "Do Not Track" preferences that may be available in your browser for letting websites know that you do not want them collecting certain kinds of information. Specifically, if you turn on the Do Not Track setting on your browser, the Site is not currently capable of following whatever Do Not Track preferences you set. For more information about Do Not Track, visit donottrack.us.

### Transfer of Data from Outside the United States

If you use the Site from outside the United States, information that we collect about you through the Site will be transferred to servers inside the United States and maintained indefinitely. By using the Site, you consent to the transfer of data into the United States, and the processing of such data in the United States.

### Children

The Site is not designed to appeal to persons under 13 years of age (children). We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from children through the Site. If we learn that any unauthorized personal information of a child has been collected, we will take appropriate steps to delete such information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child has provided any such personal information to us, you may contact us at the email or mailing address noted at the end of this privacy policy and request that we delete that information from our systems.

### Privacy Policies of any Linked Website or Other Parties

This privacy policy only addresses Valley Vet's practices for the personal and other information that we may obtain about you through the Site, or through your other communications with Valley Vet. Please be aware that when you use or access the Site, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control, and Valley Vet is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties, or the content of linked websites. We would expect that most, if not all of these third parties will collect information about you when you use their offerings. But Valley Vet is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties, regardless of whether they are linked or otherwise connected to the Site. We encourage you to read the posted privacy policy and terms of use whenever interacting with any third-party website, app, or other offering.

### Your California Privacy Rights

Sometimes we may share information collected about you with our affiliates and other third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Under California law, a California resident with whom we have an established relationship has the right to request certain information regarding the types of personal information that we have shared with third parties for these purposes, and the identities of those third parties-within the preceding calendar year, subject to certain exceptions. All requests for such information must be in writing and sent to us at service@valleyvet.com.

### Governing Law, Jurisdiction, and Dispute Resolution

The Site (excluding any linked sites) is controlled by Valley Vet from our offices within the state of Kansas, in the United States of America. It can be accessed from all 50 states, as well as from other countries around the world. As each of these places has laws that may differ from those of Kansas, by accessing or attempting to access the Site, you and Valley Vet agree that any claim, cause of action, or dispute between you and Valley Vet will be governed by and construed under the statutes and laws of the state of Kansas, without regard to the related conflict-of-laws rules and the United Nations Convention on the International Sales of Goods. This includes, without limitation, any claim, cause of action, or dispute relating to your use or attempted use of the Site; your interactions and communications with Valley Vet; Valley Vet's collection, use, and disclosure of your personal or other information; and your privacy, whether such claims are based in contract, tort, statute, or other legal basis. You and Valley Vet agree and submit to the exclusive personal jurisdiction of any court of competent jurisdiction within the state of Kansas with respect to such matters.

You also agree that any and all claims, causes of action, and disputes between you and Valley Vet are governed by the dispute resolution provisions in the Terms of Use and other agreements applicable to the Site, including the provisions for binding arbitration, waiver of the right to a jury trial, and waiver of the right to participate in a class, consolidated, or representative action. By using or attempting to use the Site, you also agree to the limitation of liability provision in the Terms of Use and other agreements applicable to the Site for any and all claims, causes of action, and disputes between you and Valley Vet, including for any claims, causes of action, or disputes related to your privacy, our use of your personal or other information collected through the Site or otherwise, and the issues addressed in this privacy policy.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time, by updating the privacy policy posted on the Site. Such changes to this privacy policy will be effective immediately upon posting them. We include the effective date of our privacy policy at the top of the statement. We encourage you to check the Site frequently to see the current privacy policy in effect, and any changes that may have been made to it. If we make material changes to the privacy policy, we will post the revised privacy policy and the revised effective date on the Site. Your continued use of the Site after a change has been posted constitutes your acceptance of the change. If you disagree with any changes to this privacy policy, your sole remedy is to discontinue your use of the Site.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy or the Site, please email us at service@valleyvet.com, or write to us at Valley Vet Supply, 1118 Pony Express Hwy., Marysville, Kansas 66508.

[

### **CALL TOLL FREE**  
800-419-9524

](tel:800-419-9524)
